<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Bo&#39;s Log | What I cannot create, I do not understand</title>
    <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bo&#39;s Log | What I cannot create, I do not understand</description>
    <image>
      <title>Bo&#39;s Log | What I cannot create, I do not understand</title>
      <url>https://csc-bo.github.io/favicon.ico</url>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/favicon.ico</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.4</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:30:19 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://csc-bo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes for CS231n: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/cs231p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:30:19 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/cs231p3/</guid>
      <description>Generative and Interactive Visual Intelligence Lecture 12: Self-supervised Learning Pretext tasks Contrastive learning Multisensory supervision Lecture 13: Generative Models Generative Adversarial Network Diffusion models Autoregressive models Lecture 14: OpenAI Sora Diffusion models Lecture 15: Robot Learning Deep Reinforcement Learning Model Learning Robotic Manipulation Lecture 16: Human-Centered Artificial Intelligence Lecture 17: Guest Lecture by Prof. Serena Yeung-Levy Lecture 18: 3D Vision 3D shape representations Shape reconstruction Neural implicit representations </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes for CS231n: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/cs231p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:30:19 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/cs231p2/</guid>
      <description>Perceiving and Understanding the Visual World Lecture 5: Image Classification with CNNs History https://zhuanlan.zhihu.com/p/352438848 Higher-level representations, image features Convolution and pooling Lecture 6: CNN Architectures Batch Normalization Transfer learning AlexNet, VGG, GoogLeNet, ResNet Lecture 7: Recurrent Neural Networks RNN, LSTM, GRU Language modeling Image captioning Sequence-to-sequence Lecture 8: Attention and Transformers Self-Attention Transformers Lecture 9: Object Detection and Image Segmentation Single-stage detectors Two-stage detectors Semantic/Instance/Panoptic segmentation Lecture 10: Video Understanding Video classification 3D CNNs Two-stream networks Multimodal video understanding Lecture 11: Visualizing and Understanding Feature visualization and inversion Adversarial examples DeepDream and style transfer </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes for CS231n: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/cs231/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:30:19 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/cs231/</guid>
      <description>Assignments Assignment #1 Image Classification, kNN, SVM, Softmax, Fully Connected Neural Network Assignment #2 Fully Connected and Convolutional Nets, Batch Normalization, Dropout, Pytorch &amp;amp; Network Visualization Assignment #3 Image Captioning with RNNs and Transformers, Network Visualization, Generative Adversarial Networks, Self-Supervised Contrastive Learning Deep Learning Basics Lecture 1: Computer vision overview
Lecture 2: Image Classification with linear Classifiers
The data-driven approch What is data-driven approaches linear classification &amp;amp; kNN means? Data-Driven Approach: 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap for machine lerning</title>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/roadmap_ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:14:51 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/roadmap_ml/</guid>
      <description>Machine Learning Courses UofT MAT334 Complex Variables MAT223&amp;amp;MAT224 Linear Algebra I&amp;amp;II MAT236 Vector Calculus STA302H1/STA1001: Methods of Data Analysis I MIT 6.S191 Introduction to Deep Learning Sequence to Sequence Computer Vision Reinforcement Learning Generative Modeling Lab 1: Tensorflow, Tensor, Auto differentiation, GradientTape, RNN Lab 2: MNIST, CNN, VAEs, Debiasing Facial Detection extra lab llm finetune self driving Standford Artificial Intelligence a. CS 221 b. At least four of: CS 223A, 224N, 224S, 224U, 224V, 224W, 228, 229, 231A, 231N, 234, 237A, 237B, 238 c.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning FAQ</title>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:10:45 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://csc-bo.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is Deep Learning? Deep learning is a subfield of artificial intelligence (AI) that focuses on training artificial neural networks to learn and make intelligent decisions. These networks are inspired by the structure and function of the human brain, and they can learn from vast amounts of data to perform tasks such as image recognition, natural language processing, and machine translation.
How does Deep Learning work? Deep learning models are typically composed of multiple layers of interconnected nodes, known as neurons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes for MIT 6.S191</title>
      <link>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/mit6s191/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:52:19 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://csc-bo.github.io/posts/mit6s191/</guid>
      <description>1. Introduction to Deep Learning After watch one of Feifei Li and Geffery Hinton&amp;rsquo;s video on Youtube, I start to gain interest in DeepLearning, then I found this MIT course online that is a very comprehensive introduction for the Deep Learning which perfect for beginners like myself. This blog post marks the beginning of my journey into the world of machine learning, serving as a collection for my course notes and insights from related materials.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
